Mr. Qin Jr.,
do you want to have sex with me?
If you
really want to do so,
then our relationship will be different.
Actually, I've got enough scandals,
and one more about being coerced
into sexual favors
wouldn't make any difference.
I just wonder if Councilman Qin's
current election
will be affected or not.
Miss Wen, that's not what I meant.
Since you were drunk,
I just wanted to bring you here to rest.
You're very interesting, Miss Wen.
See you next time.
I found out.
[Dearest Episode 5]
You're right.
Jiang Yu is indeed the son of
the deceased, Jiang Yuqing.
Just as expected.
He must not have expected
that Qin Yue had
the same custom lighter as him.
Such a small act of male rivalry
exposed his purpose and identity.
He hid it very well.
It took me a lot of effort
to find these out.
What are you going to do now?
Tell him the truth directly?
Tell him that
I wasn't the one
who ran over his mother?
Tell him the real killer
is his biological father,
He Mu?
Jiang Yu.
Come back to Dad, okay?
I have everything now.
I can compensate you
with everything you want.
I can destroy Wen Jianan,
take over the Wen Group,
and even make the Wen family
bear the surname of He.
I didn't expect my stepfather, He Mu,
to be Jiang Yu's biological father.
You know he's Jiang Yuqing's son
and he hates you very much.
-Why do you keep him around?
-Shang Yu.
Only if he hates me
can I take advantage of him.
If he can't even figure this out,
or if
he's so blinded by hatred
that he can't see the truth,
then he doesn't deserve to be my weapon.
Councilman Qin,
long time no see.
Since we last parted,
I have been expecting
[Councilman Qin, Qin Yue's Father]
to ask for your advice again.
You flatter me, Mr. He.
Wen Group has been doing great lately.
You manage it well.
No matter how big the business gets,
it can't do without your protection.
Everyone,
I'm very happy to be here today
to announce a piece of good news.
The movie "Above the Fog", invested in
and funded by Wansheng Group
and directed by Director Chen,
has already had a new candidate
for the female lead.
We will soon hold a global audition
for the most suitable soul.
Regardless of nationality or experience,
as long as the one resonates
with this role,
she is the one we are looking for.
Miss Wen,
why don't you stay a little longer?
As a female friend,
I accompanied you to so many parties
and helped you secure a lot of business.
Maybe I overestimated myself
when I was with you.
What do you mean by that, Miss Wen?
Isn't this what you wanted?
Fairness
and justice.
Of course.
I will continue to work hard
to prove to everyone
that I am the best candidate.
I have seen
your efforts.
Mr. Qin,
I hope you like the gift I gave you.
Jianan,
let me introduce you.
This is Councilman Qin,
Mr. Qin Jr.'s father.
Councilman Qin,
this is my daughter Jianan.
Nice to meet you.
Goodbye.
Wen Jianan.
Boss, the restoration results are in.
My mom was pushed from a high place.
That night,
no one knew He Mu's whereabouts.
We checked all the surveillance footage
we could,
and found that He Mu's car
also went up the winding mountain
road before the incident.
Also, the paternity test report
for you and Wen Jianan is in.
You two share no blood ties.
She is not He Mu's daughter.
Where is she now?
Our men have been keeping an eye on her.
He Mu.
How dare you trick me!
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed
is powered off.
I've long heard that Miss Wen is a beauty.
Seeing you today, I found
you truly live up to your reputation.
Let me go!
If you dare do anything to me,
the Wen family won't let you off,
and neither will Qin Yue.
Get lost!
Let me go!
Help!
Let her go!
Wen Jianan. Wen Jianan.
♪ In the darkness
where there is no light ♪
♪ At the end of every lonely night ♪
Wen Jianan.
♪ Now my heart is beating once again ♪
Let's go home.
♪ Finally I'm breathing past the pain ♪
♪ In the winter breeze,
I feel your breath ♪
♪ Waking up my soul from frozen death ♪
♪ Like a miracle, you came in view ♪
♪ At the edge of this breaking world ♪
♪ You are the only one
who brought the light ♪
♪ Because it's you ♪
♪ All my sorrows ♪
♪ Fading out of sight ♪
♪ In your arms, I'm born again and new ♪
How is she doing?
Fortunately, she wasn't seriously injured.
She will recover
after resting for a while.
It's just...
Just what?
You'd better go in and see for yourself.
Thank you.
Wen Jianan? Wen Jianan?
Are you okay?
Jiang Yu.
I'm burning up.
You are so handsome.
Can you help me?
Calm down. You've been drugged.